Suri Gudugu Patti Bade Bhuj Mut Chim Chicken
Needle
T Rendal Kaap Kadi
[Music]
Kava Aakasam I Pet Mu Palm Muti And Bhag Bhag
Ti Chinuk
[Music]
Tad Up Kalag Munil
Father Katmo
Kade Kala Lakad
Ville D Garjan D Upan Barsi
Praya Sag D Military Kd Churchi Kalite Dayan
Mein Okari Kokani Namam Nachin Snehme
Ile Noore
[Music]
Nivale
[Music] Marbles Kade Ad Manche Bar Kak Chirk Temra Kasi Dahle Vegam Kd Tyag Mak Gatam Maruva Gamanam Okari Kokani Namam Nachin
Snehme
Ile Noore
[Praise]
[Music]
Nivale
Suri Gudugu Patti Bade Bhuj Mut Chim Chicken Needle T Rendal Kaap Kadi
[Music]
Kava Three to
One
[Music] Say
Again Say Again Thank You Thank
You Triple Thank You Triple Thank You Triple Thank You
Triple
Thank You
Thank
You Thank You
Thank You Thank You Thank
You